export const quizData = [
  {
    question: "Which team has won the most Premier League titles?",
    a: "Chelsea",
    b: "Manchester City",
    c: "Manchester United",
    d: "Liverpool",
    correct: "c",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who holds the record for the most goals scored in a single Premier League season?",
    a: "Thierry Henry",
    b: "Alan Shearer",
    c: "Mohamed Salah",
    d: "Erling Haaland",
    correct: "d",
  },
  {
    question: "Which Premier League club is nicknamed The Toffees?",
    a: "Newcastle United",
    b: "West Ham United",
    c: "Everton",
    d: "Aston Villa",
    correct: "c",
  },
  {
    question: "Who was the first Premier League manager to be knighted?",
    a: "Sir Alex Ferguson",
    b: "Sir Bobby Robson",
    c: "Sir Kenny Dalglish",
    d: "Sir Matt Busby",
    correct: "a",
  },
  {
    question: "Which club went an entire Premier League season unbeaten?",
    a: "Chelsea",
    b: "Arsenal",
    c: "Manchester City",
    d: "Liverpool",
    correct: "b",
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the Premier League's all-time leading goal scorer?",
    a: "Wayne Rooney",
    b: "Frank Lampard",
    c: "Alan Shearer",
    d: "Sergio Ag√ºero",
    correct: "c",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which player has made the most appearances in the Premier League?",
    a: "Ryan Giggs",
    b: "Frank Lampard",
    c: "Gareth Barry",
    d: "Steven Gerrard",
    correct: "c",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following teams has never been relegated from the Premier League since its inception?",
    a: "Aston Villa",
    b: "Everton",
    c: "Leeds United",
    d: "West Ham United",
    correct: "b",
  },
  {
    question: "Who won the Premier League Golden Boot for the 2022-23 season?",
    a: "Harry Kane",
    b: "Mohamed Salah",
    c: "Erling Haaland",
    d: "Son Heung-min",
    correct: "c",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which team holds the record for the longest winning streak in Premier League history?",
    a: "Manchester United",
    b: "Chelsea",
    c: "Manchester City",
    d: "Liverpool",
    correct: "c",
  },
];
